[{"answer": " Hi, my friend", "docId": "You-Can-Count-On-Me.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "OK.  Be right back, you guys", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "We're supposed to write a story for English homework, but they didn't tell us what it's supposed to be about", "docId": "You-Can-Count-On-Me.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I mean they didn't tell us what it's supposed to be about. They said do whatever you want", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Mr. my friend", "docId": "You-Can-Count-On-Me.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "my friend. Hi. I'm my friend", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Yeah..", "docId": "You-Can-Count-On-Me.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "-- I know, I haven't been", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "It was just bullshit..", "docId": "You-Can-Count-On-Me.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "I didn't do anything. Does it occur to you that maybe I was wronged", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "I really wish Mom was here", "docId": "You-Can-Count-On-Me.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Nobody knows what to do with you", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Come on, my friend, can we not talk about that shit", "docId": "You-Can-Count-On-Me.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Um", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Yeah. Thanks", "docId": "You-Can-Count-On-Me.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Good night", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "I know. They're my parents too", "docId": "You-Can-Count-On-Me.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Well, yeah. Your mom is my sister", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Try it", "docId": "You-Can-Count-On-Me.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Well, the way you hold it is wrong", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Oh", "docId": "You-Can-Count-On-Me.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Well, I did work it out", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Who are you talking about", "docId": "You-Can-Count-On-Me.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Were you a wild kid", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Why", "docId": "You-Can-Count-On-Me.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "I know, I know, but it's so... There's nothing to do here", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "It's just", "docId": "You-Can-Count-On-Me.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Why? He's not gonna do anything different than what I'm doing", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Great. What are we supposed to do now", "docId": "You-Can-Count-On-Me.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "I've played it", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "You-Can-Count-On-Me.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "I mean, I know I haven't exactly been the most... decisive... guy. In the past... I don't kno", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": " He", "docId": "You-Can-Count-On-Me.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": " Hey", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "I won't", "docId": "You-Can-Count-On-Me.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "I won't", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "No", "docId": "You-Can-Count-On-Me.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "That's it. She's pregnant", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Anyway... We'll work it out..", "docId": "You-Can-Count-On-Me.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "I could use a tranquilizer", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Fine", "docId": "You-Can-Count-On-Me.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Yes, the fucking plumber came", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Uh huh. And what do you", "docId": "You-Can-Count-On-Me.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "First of all, he didn't tell me anythin", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "I'm sorry", "docId": "You-Can-Count-On-Me.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "Of course I've been thinking about it", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "I don't know... I... Maybe this is... Last year I sort of thought you were possibly interested in that... idea... but I was the one who, you know, wasn't", "docId": "You-Can-Count-On-Me.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": " I don't want you to feel bad for me", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "And I also find it kind of discouraging that you seem to think I need some kind of spiritual counseling or what have you, so much so that you're willing to disregard the fact that I don't believe in any of this stuff at all", "docId": "You-Can-Count-On-Me.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "I mean it's really kind of insulting", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "Why not", "docId": "You-Can-Count-On-Me.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "I don't want to go fishing with Father my friend", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "Um... No", "docId": "You-Can-Count-On-Me.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "Well... Why do you think you're in this situation", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": " Who is it", "docId": "You-Can-Count-On-Me.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": " How old is he", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "You-Can-Count-On-Me.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "Oh, that wasn't my father", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "You-Can-Count-On-Me.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "No", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "That wasn't him. I heard him tell the cops", "docId": "You-Can-Count-On-Me.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": " No it wasn't", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": "What do you mean, Get my own place", "docId": "You-Can-Count-On-Me.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": "You mean in that place", "qsentId": 64}, {"answer": "Look. I know you're upset about Uncle my friend leaving, and so am I. But he's just not in control of himself, and I don't want him hurting your feelings anymore", "docId": "You-Can-Count-On-Me.txt", "asentId": 67, "question": "You don't care. I don't care either", "qsentId": 66}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "You-Can-Count-On-Me.txt", "asentId": 69, "question": "All right", "qsentId": 68}]